# Hiu Wing, Lam

University graduate with computer science major. Proficient in a range of modern technologies including Microsoft Office software, Photoshop, Premiere, HTML, CSS and MySQL. Can work well both independently and in a team. Experience working in the service industry with the understanding of customer service. Hard-working, very patient, proactive individual with strong problem-solving and the ability to learn new concepts fast.

## **Education**

**BS** in Computer Science

08/2018 - 12/2020

Brooklyn College. Brooklyn, NY

GPA: 3.35 / 4.00

#### **Relevant Coursework:**

 Design and Implementation Web Application, Database Systems, Computer Architecture, Data Structure, Operation Systems, Analysis of Algorithms in Computer Science, Discrete Structure in Computer Science

Honors & Awards: Dean's List (2020)

**AAS in Computer Information System** 

03/2017 - 06/2018

Kingsborough Community College. Brooklyn, NY

GPA: 3.41 / 4.00

#### Relevant Coursework:

 Object-Oriented Programming, Network Server Administration, Advance Personal Computer Techniques for Business, Advance Programming Techniques, Web Page Development, Java for Programmers

## **Extracurricular Activities**

#### SBUHacks 2020

September 25-26, 2020

## **Description:**

 A 24 hour hackathon where students are challenged to further what they know by doing projects on what they are passionate about.

## My Project: Gaia - A mobile app

• This app will help individuals calculating their carbon footprint consumption, offers a personalized recommendation on the "quick wins" action that they can do based on their inputs, and offer a donate feature for them that will be used to fund environmental and conservation acts. With this, users will be fully aware of their significant involvement in this issue and have the chance to act straight away to offset the negative externalities that they have caused.

## **Personal Information**

Address:

531, 51st Street, Brooklyn,

NY 11220

■ Phone:

646-853-6534

■ E-mail:

hilda11224@gmail.com

**■** Personal Website:

https://hiuwing0107.github.io/PersonalWebsitePortfolio

■ GitHub:

https://github.com/hiuwing0107?
t ab=repositories

# **Technical Skills**

Java: 4 years

• HTML/CSS: 4 years

• **PHP**: 2 year

JavaScript: 2 years

MySQL Database: 2 year

• Figma: 1 years

Adobe Photoshop: 3 years

Adobe Premiere: 3 years

• Skills in Mircosoft Office: 4 years

## <u>Languages</u>

- English
- Chinese (Cantonese)
- Chinese (Mandarin)

1

# **Work Experiences**

Office Clerk 07/2021 - 08/2022

**US Elogistics Service Corp. Monroe Township, NJ** 

### Key Qualifications & Responsibilities:

- Transferred product information and data into computer files and database database
- Updated the existing data, checked and analysed the quality of the products
- · Organized, categorized, and separated products and materials
- · Scanned products barcode and filed the data into the OWMS system
- Maintained spreadsheets for various reports and made an oral report to the manager

## **Customer Receptionist**

08/2018 - Present

## Running Kids.Inc, Kids Indoor Playground. Brooklyn, NY

## Key Qualifications & Responsibilities:

- Greeted and welcomed guests and provided them with a positive first impression of the company
- · Handled incoming calls and took the messages from customers
- Directed customers and deal with their complaints or problems
- Picked up the order and collected customer's payments through the POS system
- · Scheduled and confirmed the party reservation

#### **Restaurant Server**

01/2016 - 02/2017

# Formosa Cuisine, Asian and Vegetarian Restaurant. Poughkeepsie, NY Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- · Greeted and escorted customers to their tables
- · Presented menu and provided detailed information when asked
- Arranged table settings and maintained a tidy dining area
- · Handled incoming calls and took the delivery orders
- Picked up the order and collected customer's payments through the POS system
- · Delivered food and drinks to the customers' tables

## **Interests**

- Designing Websites
- Video Editing
- Traveling
- Listening to Music